export const library = [
  {
    question: "translate to english: Huhn",
    answer: "chicken",
    category: "Food",
    id: "asdfasdfassg134124",
    book: "Basic English",
  },
  {
    question: "translate to english: Gurke",
    answer: "cucumber",
    category: "Food",
    id: "gverigno23525",
    book: "Basic English",
  },
  {
    question: "translate to english: Auto",
    answer: "car",
    category: "Vehicles",
    id: "verinoj0982345",
    book: "Basic English",
  },
  {
    question: "translate to english: Fahrrad",
    answer: "bicycle",
    category: "Vehicles",
    id: "perigj0923852039",
    book: "Basic English",
  },
  {
    question: "Eine Flasche Wasser",
    answer: "a bottle of water",
    category: "Food",
    id: "pegjfpojg0832059ufij",
    book: "Basic English",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Javascript array method that returns a new array iterator object that contains the key/value pairs for each index in the array.",
    answer: "entries",
    category: "Javascript",
    id: "epwgoj3084203948",
    book: "Basic English",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Javascript array method that applies a function against an accumulator and each value of the array (from right-to-left) to reduce it to a single value.",
    answer: "reduceright",
    category: "Javascript",
    id: "sdlfkj234234lksdjf",
    book: "General Knowledge",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Javascript array method that changes the contents of an array by removing or replacing existing elements and/or adding new elements in place.",
    answer: "splice",
    category: "Javascript",
    id: "wpwoejf234234",
    book: "General Knowledge",
  },
  {
    question: "What is a group of flamingos called?",
    answer: "flamboyance",
    category: "Flamingo Facts",
    id: "wpij2p3523potg2",
    book: "General Knowledge",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the nests of flamingos made of?",
    answer: "mud",
    category: "Flamingo Facts",
    id: "wifj2p35j2p35ijfwe",
    book: "General Knowledge",
  },
  {
    question: "How large (in cm) can the largest flamingos in the world grow?",
    answer: "187",
    category: "Flamingo Facts",
    id: "wfj2342308ÃŸ9fujwpoejf",
    book: "General Knowledge",
  },
  {
    question: "how many eggs do flamingos lay in a year?",
    answer: "1",
    category: "Flamingo Facts",
    id: "elkfj3jr2p3or",
    book: "General Knowledge",
  },
];
